var stage1 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of productivity",
    "answer": "PRODUCT",
    "hint": "PDUT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of rusty",
    "answer": "RUST",
    "hint": "RT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of predictive",
    "answer": "PREDICT",
    "hint": "PEICT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of constitution",
    "answer": "CONSULT",
    "hint": "CLT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": " What city is the capital of vindication",
    "answer": "VINDICATE",
    "hint": "VNDTE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abandoned",
    "answer": "ABANDON",
    "hint": "ABNN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of egotist",
    "answer": "EGO",
    "hint": "EO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of acting",
    "answer": "ACT",
    "hint": "AT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of legalities",
    "answer": "LEGAL",
    "hint": "LGL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of kilometer",
    "answer": "METER",
    "hint": "MTR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of arboretum",
    "answer": "ARBOR",
    "hint": "ARR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cryptic",
    "answer": "CRYPT",
    "hint": "CYT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of paranormal",
    "answer": "NORM",
    "hint": "NM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hydrophobia",
    "answer": "PHOBIA",
    "hint": "PHIA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of information",
    "answer": "FORM",
    "hint": "FM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of herbivore",
    "answer": "VOR",
    "hint": "VR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of senator",
    "answer": "SEN",
    "hint": "SN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of telephone",
    "answer": "TELE",
    "hint": "TLE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of consent",
    "answer": "SENT",
    "hint": "SN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of acridity",
    "answer": "ACRI",
    "hint": "ARI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of corporal",
    "answer": "CORP",
    "hint": "CRP",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of astronaut",
    "answer": "ASTRO",
    "hint": "ASO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of reincarnate",
    "answer": "CARN",
    "hint": "CN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of audible",
    "answer": "AUD",
    "hint": "AD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of beneficial",
    "answer": "BENE",
    "hint": "BNE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of autonomy",
    "answer": "AUTO",
    "hint": "ATO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of diction",
    "answer": "DICT",
    "hint": "DC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of incredible",
    "answer": "CRED",
    "hint": "CED",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of faculty",
    "answer": "FAC",
    "hint": "FC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of genesis",
    "answer": "GEN",
    "hint": "GN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of metastasis",
    "answer": "META",
    "hint": "MTA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hemicycle",
    "answer": "HEMI",
    "hint": "HMI",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage2 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of microcosm",
    "answer": "MICRO",
    "hint": "MRO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of luminary",
    "answer": "LUM",
    "hint": "LM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of multilingual",
    "answer": "MULTI",
    "hint": "MLT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of transport",
    "answer": "PORT",
    "hint": "PRT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sectional",
    "answer": "SECT",
    "hint": "ST",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ambulance",
    "answer": "AMBUL",
    "hint": "AMU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of electrocardiogram",
    "answer": "CARDIO",
    "hint": "RDIO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of intercede",
    "answer": "CEDE",
    "hint": "CE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of equilateral",
    "answer": "EQUI",
    "hint": "EUI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of epidermis",
    "answer": "DERM",
    "hint": "DRM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of counteract",
    "answer": "COUNTER",
    "hint": "CUTR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of demographic",
    "answer": "DEM",
    "hint": "DM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hypnotic",
    "answer": "HYPNO",
    "hint": "HPO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of intravenous",
    "answer": "INTRA",
    "hint": "INR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of reject",
    "answer": "JECT",
    "hint": "JCT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of magnify",
    "answer": "MAGNI",
    "hint": "MNI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of malfunction",
    "answer": "MAL",
    "hint": "ML",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of omnivore",
    "answer": "OMNI",
    "hint": "ONI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of paternity",
    "answer": "PATER",
    "hint": "PTR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of scripture",
    "answer": "SCRIPT",
    "hint": "SRPT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of envision",
    "answer": "VIS",
    "hint": "VS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abasement",
    "answer": "ABASE",
    "hint": "ABE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of baronetcy",
    "answer": "BARON",
    "hint": "BRN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abatement",
    "answer": "ABATE",
    "hint": "AAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of barrenness",
    "answer": "BARREN",
    "hint": "BRRN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abbreviation",
    "answer": "ABBREVIATE",
    "hint": "ABBAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bathe",
    "answer": "BATH",
    "hint": "BH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of basement",
    "answer": "BASE",
    "hint": "BSE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abdication",
    "answer": "ABDICATE",
    "hint": "AIAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bashfully",
    "answer": "BASH",
    "hint": "BH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sophism",
    "answer": "SOPH",
    "hint": "SPH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of antecedent",
    "answer": "ANTE",
    "hint": "ATE",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage3 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abdominal",
    "answer": "ABDOMEN",
    "hint": "ADEN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bawdiness",
    "answer": "BAWDY",
    "hint": "BAD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of beatifically",
    "answer": "BEATIFIC",
    "hint": "BTFI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abductor",
    "answer": "ABDUCT",
    "hint": "AUC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bearable",
    "answer": "BEAR",
    "hint": "BER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of aberrance",
    "answer": "ABERRANT",
    "hint": "ARRNT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bewilderment",
    "answer": "BEWILDER",
    "hint": "BWLD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abnormality",
    "answer": "NORMAL",
    "hint": "NRM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of benevolence",
    "answer": "BENEVOLENT",
    "hint": "BNELE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abettor",
    "answer": "ABET",
    "hint": "AET",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of accompanist",
    "answer": "ACCOMPANY",
    "hint": "ACMP",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of belatedly",
    "answer": "BELATED",
    "hint": "BLAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abjectly",
    "answer": "ABJECT",
    "hint": "AJE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of beggary",
    "answer": "BEGGAR",
    "hint": "BGGR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ably",
    "answer": "ABLE",
    "hint": "ALE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bigotry",
    "answer": "BIGOT",
    "hint": "BGO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of beryllium",
    "answer": "BERYL",
    "hint": "BRY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of absorbent",
    "answer": "ABSORB",
    "hint": "ASOR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bisection",
    "answer": "SECT",
    "hint": "SCT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of absence",
    "answer": "ABSENT",
    "hint": "ABEN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bemusement",
    "answer": "BEMUSE",
    "hint": "BMUS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of blandishment",
    "answer": "BLAND",
    "hint": "BLN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abusively",
    "answer": "ABUSE",
    "hint": "AUS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of beneficent",
    "answer": "BENEFIT",
    "hint": "BENE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abstention",
    "answer": "ABSTAIN",
    "hint": "ASTA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abhorrence",
    "answer": "ABHOR",
    "hint": "ABH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": " What city is the capital of barometric",
    "answer": "BARO",
    "hint": "BR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abolition",
    "answer": "ABOLISH",
    "hint": "ALI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of basilica",
    "answer": "BASIL",
    "hint": "AIL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bigamous",
    "answer": "BIGAMY",
    "hint": "GMY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sediment",
    "answer": "SED",
    "hint": "SD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of malajusted",
    "answer": "MAL",
    "hint": "ML",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage4 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of accentuate",
    "answer": "ACCENT",
    "hint": "ACC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of benignity",
    "answer": "BENIGN",
    "hint": "BNIN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bathetic",
    "answer": "BATHOS",
    "hint": "BTHS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of aboriginal",
    "answer": "ABROGINIE",
    "hint": "ARGNI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of betrothal",
    "answer": "BETROTH",
    "hint": "ROTH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bereavement",
    "answer": "BEREFT",
    "hint": "BRF",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abortive",
    "answer": "ABORT",
    "hint": "ART",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of berkelium",
    "answer": "BERK",
    "hint": "BRK",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bishopric",
    "answer": "BISHOP",
    "hint": "BIP",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bituminous",
    "answer": "BITUMEN",
    "hint": "BTMN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abridgement",
    "answer": "BRIDGE",
    "hint": "BRGE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bowdlerization",
    "answer": "BOW",
    "hint": "BW",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bivouacked",
    "answer": "BIVOUAC",
    "hint": "BVUA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of academician",
    "answer": "ACADEMIC",
    "hint": "ADEMC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bombardier",
    "answer": "BOMB",
    "hint": "BMB",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of boutique",
    "answer": "BOUT",
    "hint": "BOT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of brigadier",
    "answer": "BRIG",
    "hint": "BRG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bittiness",
    "answer": "BITTY",
    "hint": "BTT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abtting",
    "answer": "ABUT",
    "hint": "AUT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of buggery",
    "answer": "BUG",
    "hint": "BG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bitch",
    "answer": "BIT",
    "hint": "BT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of blouson",
    "answer": "BLOUSE",
    "hint": "BLSE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of buffalo",
    "answer": "BUFF",
    "hint": "BFF",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ambiguous",
    "answer": "AMBI",
    "hint": "ABI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of aquarium",
    "answer": "AQUA",
    "hint": "AUA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of advocate",
    "answer": "VOC",
    "hint": "VC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of destruction",
    "answer": "SRUCT",
    "hint": "SRT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bankrupt",
    "answer": "RUPT",
    "hint": "RPT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of mortician",
    "answer": "MORT",
    "hint": "MRT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of video",
    "answer": "VID",
    "hint": "VD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hemoglobin",
    "answer": "HEMA",
    "hint": "HMA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of metric",
    "answer": "METRY",
    "hint": "MTY",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage5 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of transmit",
    "answer": "MIT",
    "hint": "MT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of inspection",
    "answer": "SPECT",
    "hint": "SPT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of material",
    "answer": "MATER",
    "hint": "MTR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of prejudice",
    "answer": "JUD",
    "hint": "JD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of fracture",
    "answer": "FRACT",
    "hint": "FAC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of century",
    "answer": "CENT",
    "hint": "CT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of prescribe",
    "answer": "SCRIBE",
    "hint": "SRB",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of induce",
    "answer": "DUC",
    "hint": "DC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of chronological",
    "answer": "CHRON",
    "hint": "CON",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dysfunctional",
    "answer": "DYS",
    "hint": "DS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of anthropologist",
    "answer": "ANTHROPO",
    "hint": "THPO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of circumstance",
    "answer": "CIRCUM",
    "hint": "RM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of telegram",
    "answer": "GRAM",
    "hint": "AM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of fortitude",
    "answer": "FORT",
    "hint": "FT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of phonograph",
    "answer": "GRAPH",
    "hint": "GRA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of heteronym",
    "answer": "HETERO",
    "hint": "HTRO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hydration",
    "answer": "HYDR",
    "hint": "HDR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of misanthrope",
    "answer": "MIS",
    "hint": "MS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of biology",
    "answer": "BIO",
    "hint": "BO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of philosophy",
    "answer": "PHIL",
    "hint": "PL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of monologue",
    "answer": "MONO",
    "hint": "MNO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of phone",
    "answer": "PHON",
    "hint": "PON",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hypothetical",
    "answer": "HYPO",
    "hint": "HPO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of microscope",
    "answer": "SCOPE",
    "hint": "SPE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of antonym",
    "answer": "NYM",
    "hint": "NM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of phosphorous",
    "answer": "PHOS",
    "hint": "POS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of morphology",
    "answer": "MORPH",
    "hint": "MRH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of homogenous",
    "answer": "HOMO",
    "hint": "HMO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dynamic",
    "answer": "DYNA",
    "hint": "YA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of psychology",
    "answer": "LOGY",
    "hint": "LGY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of plausible",
    "answer": "PLAUS",
    "hint": "AUS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of chronological",
    "answer": "CHRONO",
    "hint": "CHNO",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage6 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of misogyny",
    "answer": "MISO",
    "hint": "MSO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of photograph",
    "answer": "PHOTO",
    "hint": "PHTO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of thermal",
    "answer": "THERM",
    "hint": "TRM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bibliophile",
    "answer": "BIBLIO",
    "hint": "BLIO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of psychology",
    "answer": "PSYCHO",
    "hint": "SYCH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of antibacterial",
    "answer": "ANTI",
    "hint": "ATI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of techological",
    "answer": "TECHNO",
    "hint": "ENO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pseudoscience",
    "answer": "PSEUDO",
    "hint": "SEO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of astronaut",
    "answer": "AST",
    "hint": "AT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of chronic",
    "answer": "CHRONO",
    "hint": "CHNO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of theologian",
    "answer": "LOGOS",
    "hint": "LGS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of kinetic",
    "answer": "KINESIS",
    "hint": "KNSS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of aquarium",
    "answer": "AQU",
    "hint": "AU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of phytochrome",
    "answer": "CHROME",
    "hint": "CRME",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of document",
    "answer": "DOC",
    "hint": "DC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of geography",
    "answer": "GEO",
    "hint": "GO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of asteroid",
    "answer": "ASTER",
    "hint": "ATER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of narcotic",
    "answer": "NARC",
    "hint": "NR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of empahty",
    "answer": "PATH",
    "hint": "PTH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of abstract",
    "answer": "AB",
    "hint": "A",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dictate",
    "answer": "DICT",
    "hint": "DC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of tropical",
    "answer": "TROPOS",
    "hint": "ROS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of circulate",
    "answer": "CIRC",
    "hint": "CR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of exacerbate",
    "answer": "ACER",
    "hint": "CE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of brief",
    "answer": "BREV",
    "hint": "BE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of founder",
    "answer": "FUND",
    "hint": "FND",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of inhabit",
    "answer": "HAB",
    "hint": "HB",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of justice",
    "answer": "JUR",
    "hint": "JR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of levitate",
    "answer": "LEV",
    "hint": "LV",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of agnostic",
    "answer": "GNO",
    "hint": "GO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of zygote",
    "answer": "ZYG",
    "hint": "ZG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sonorous",
    "answer": "SON",
    "hint": "SN",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage7 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of manual",
    "answer": "MANU",
    "hint": "MU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of logic",
    "answer": "LOGUE",
    "hint": "LUE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of permit",
    "answer": "MIT",
    "hint": "MT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of tranquil",
    "answer": "QUIT",
    "hint": "QI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of lucid",
    "answer": "LUC",
    "hint": "LC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sensitive",
    "answer": "SENS",
    "hint": "EN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of extraterrest",
    "answer": "TERR",
    "hint": "ER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of timid",
    "answer": "TIM",
    "hint": "I",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of auditorium",
    "answer": "AUDI",
    "hint": "AI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of evacuate",
    "answer": "VAC",
    "hint": "VC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of photosyntesis",
    "answer": "SYN",
    "hint": "YN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of mariner",
    "answer": "MARINE",
    "hint": "ANE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of replace",
    "answer": "PLACE",
    "hint": "LCE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of heater",
    "answer": "HEAT",
    "hint": "HAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of scheme",
    "answer": "SCHEM",
    "hint": "SEM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of behaviour",
    "answer": "BEHAVE",
    "hint": "BHV",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of unwanted",
    "answer": "WANT",
    "hint": "WT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of viewed",
    "answer": "VIEW",
    "hint": "VW",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pacify",
    "answer": "PAC",
    "hint": "PC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of normality",
    "answer": "NORMAL",
    "hint": "NAL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of acronym",
    "answer": "ACRO",
    "hint": "ACO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dethrone",
    "answer": "DE",
    "hint": "D",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hepatoma",
    "answer": "HEPA",
    "hint": "HA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of midriff",
    "answer": "MID",
    "hint": "MD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pneumatic",
    "answer": "PNEUM",
    "hint": "PUM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of tripod",
    "answer": "PODE",
    "hint": "PE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of decibel",
    "answer": "DECI",
    "hint": "CI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of aerospace",
    "answer": "AER",
    "hint": "AR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of eloquent",
    "answer": "LOQU",
    "hint": "OQ",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of agrarian",
    "answer": "AGR",
    "hint": "AR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of zoology",
    "answer": "ZO",
    "hint": "Z",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of malajusted",
    "answer": "MAL",
    "hint": "AL",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage8 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of immigrant",
    "answer": "MIGR",
    "hint": "IG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of decade",
    "answer": "DECA",
    "hint": "CA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of heptagon",
    "answer": "HEPTA",
    "hint": "ETA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of metropolis",
    "answer": "POLI",
    "hint": "PLI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of analgestic",
    "answer": "ALG",
    "hint": "AG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sum",
    "answer": "SUM",
    "hint": "S",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of panacea",
    "answer": "PAN",
    "hint": "PN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of democracy",
    "answer": "DEMO",
    "hint": "DM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of millibar",
    "answer": "MILLI",
    "hint": "MLLI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ambidextrous",
    "answer": "AMBI",
    "hint": "MB",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of herbivourous",
    "answer": "HERBI",
    "hint": "ERI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of polyglot",
    "answer": "POLY",
    "hint": "OLY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of superior",
    "answer": "SUPER",
    "hint": "UPR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of amiable",
    "answer": "AMI",
    "hint": "AI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of retrograde",
    "answer": "RETRO",
    "hint": "RER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of symmetry",
    "answer": "SYM",
    "hint": "SM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of heterodox",
    "answer": "HETERO",
    "hint": "ERO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of mini",
    "answer": "MINI",
    "hint": "MIN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of demitasse",
    "answer": "DEMI",
    "hint": "DEM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of opponet",
    "answer": "PON",
    "hint": "PN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of lactose",
    "answer": "LACTO",
    "hint": "LAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hexagon",
    "answer": "HEX",
    "hint": "HX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of contact",
    "answer": "TACT",
    "hint": "TCT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of epidemic",
    "answer": "DEM",
    "hint": "DM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of analysis",
    "answer": "ANA",
    "hint": "AN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of missel",
    "answer": "MISS",
    "hint": "MS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of misandry",
    "answer": "ANDR",
    "hint": "AR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of population",
    "answer": "POP",
    "hint": "PO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of confide",
    "answer": "FID",
    "hint": "FD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of equidistant",
    "answer": "EQUI",
    "hint": "EUI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of contradict",
    "answer": "CONTRA",
    "hint": "CTRA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of endogamy",
    "answer": "ENDO",
    "hint": "EDO",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage9 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of deposit",
    "answer": "POS",
    "hint": "PS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of synchronize",
    "answer": "SYN",
    "hint": "SN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of philodendron",
    "answer": "DENDRON",
    "hint": "DERO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of immobilize",
    "answer": "MOB",
    "hint": "MB",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of histology",
    "answer": "HISTO",
    "hint": "HST",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of amorous",
    "answer": "AMO",
    "hint": "AO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of tangible",
    "answer": "TANG",
    "hint": "TAG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of syntax",
    "answer": "TAX",
    "hint": "TX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dental",
    "answer": "DENT",
    "hint": "DNT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of motion",
    "answer": "MOT",
    "hint": "MT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of homonym",
    "answer": "HOMO",
    "hint": "HOM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of preamble",
    "answer": "PRE",
    "hint": "PE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of animal",
    "answer": "ANIM",
    "hint": "AIM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cognizant",
    "answer": "COGN",
    "hint": "CGN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of biennial",
    "answer": "ANNI",
    "hint": "AN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of atheist",
    "answer": "IST",
    "hint": "IT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of posthumous",
    "answer": "POST",
    "hint": "ST",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hygrometer",
    "answer": "HYGR",
    "hint": "GR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dendriform",
    "answer": "DENDRI",
    "hint": "EI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of metamorphosis",
    "answer": "MORPH",
    "hint": "MPH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ambivalence",
    "answer": "AMPHI",
    "hint": "AHI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of taxono",
    "answer": "TAX",
    "hint": "TX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of patricide",
    "answer": "CISE",
    "hint": "CSE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of voracious",
    "answer": "CIOUS",
    "hint": "COUS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of prophet",
    "answer": "PRO",
    "hint": "PO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dentures",
    "answer": "DONT",
    "hint": "DNT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of immutable",
    "answer": "MUT",
    "hint": "MT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of anniversary",
    "answer": "ANN",
    "hint": "A",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of homeopath",
    "answer": "HOMEO",
    "hint": "HMEO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of technology",
    "answer": "TECHNO",
    "hint": "TECH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hemicycle",
    "answer": "HEMI",
    "hint": "EM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of metastasis",
    "answer": "META",
    "hint": "ET",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage10 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pantheist",
    "answer": "THEI",
    "hint": "HE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of myosin",
    "answer": "MYO",
    "hint": "O",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of antecede",
    "answer": "ANTE",
    "hint": "NT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dichromatic",
    "answer": "DI",
    "hint": "D",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hyperactive",
    "answer": "HYPER",
    "hint": "YER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of protocol",
    "answer": "PROTO",
    "hint": "ROTO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of amaranth",
    "answer": "ANTH",
    "hint": "NTH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of contemporary",
    "answer": "TEMP",
    "hint": "EMP",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of plutocracy",
    "answer": "CRACY",
    "hint": "RAC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of detention",
    "answer": "TENT",
    "hint": "EN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of iconology",
    "answer": "ICONO",
    "hint": "ION",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of narrate",
    "answer": "NARR",
    "hint": "NR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of aphorism",
    "answer": "APHO",
    "hint": "APH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pungent",
    "answer": "PUNG",
    "hint": "PG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of diploma",
    "answer": "DIPLO",
    "hint": "DPL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of incline",
    "answer": "CLINE",
    "hint": "CLN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cranial",
    "answer": "CRANIO",
    "hint": "CANI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dialog",
    "answer": "DIA",
    "hint": "DA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cumulative",
    "answer": "CUMUL",
    "hint": "MUL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of natal",
    "answer": "NAT",
    "hint": "NT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of disappear",
    "answer": "DIS",
    "hint": "DS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of idiot",
    "answer": "IDIO",
    "hint": "DI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of anthozoan",
    "answer": "ANTHO",
    "hint": "ANH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of repugnant",
    "answer": "PUGN",
    "hint": "PUG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of tenacious",
    "answer": "TEN",
    "hint": "TE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of compulsion",
    "answer": "PUL",
    "hint": "PL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of necrosis",
    "answer": "NECR",
    "hint": "NR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of diabetes",
    "answer": "DIA",
    "hint": "DA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of apology",
    "answer": "APO",
    "hint": "AO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of illuminate",
    "answer": "IL",
    "hint": "I",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sophism",
    "answer": "SOPH",
    "hint": "SH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of protoplasm",
    "answer": "PLAS",
    "hint": "PS",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage11 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of removable",
    "answer": "MOV",
    "hint": "M",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of matriarch",
    "answer": "ARCH",
    "hint": "CH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of continent",
    "answer": "TIN",
    "hint": "TN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of purge",
    "answer": "PURG",
    "hint": "RG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of attition",
    "answer": "TRIT",
    "hint": "RI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dominate",
    "answer": "DOMIN",
    "hint": "DOM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of arthroscope",
    "answer": "ARTHR",
    "hint": "RTH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of circumnavigate",
    "answer": "NAV",
    "hint": "NA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dominate",
    "answer": "DOMIN",
    "hint": "DMI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of innovation",
    "answer": "IN",
    "hint": "I",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ethnology",
    "answer": "ETHNO",
    "hint": "THN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of determine",
    "answer": "TERM",
    "hint": "ER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of heterdox",
    "answer": "HETERO",
    "hint": "HRO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of negate",
    "answer": "NEG",
    "hint": "NG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of artifact",
    "answer": "ART",
    "hint": "AT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of computer",
    "answer": "PUT",
    "hint": "UT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of impossible",
    "answer": "IM",
    "hint": "M",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of histology",
    "answer": "HISTRO",
    "hint": "ISO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of donor",
    "answer": "DON",
    "hint": "ON",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of aviary",
    "answer": "ARI",
    "hint": "AI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of terrain",
    "answer": "TERR",
    "hint": "ER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of irresponsible",
    "answer": "IR",
    "hint": "R",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of neonatal",
    "answer": "NEO",
    "hint": "NO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of donation",
    "answer": "DONAT",
    "hint": "OAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pyrometer",
    "answer": "PYR",
    "hint": "YR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of baryon",
    "answer": "BAR",
    "hint": "BA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of infrared",
    "answer": "INFRA",
    "hint": "NRA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of tetrapod",
    "answer": "TETRA",
    "hint": "TRA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of conduct",
    "answer": "DUCT",
    "hint": "UC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of nephritis",
    "answer": "NEPHR",
    "hint": "EHR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of immerse",
    "answer": "MERS",
    "hint": "MS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of antecedent",
    "answer": "ANTE",
    "hint": "TE",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage12 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of duplicate",
    "answer": "DU",
    "hint": "D",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of imagine",
    "answer": "IMAG",
    "hint": "MAG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of belligerent",
    "answer": "BELLI",
    "hint": "ELI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of quadrant",
    "answer": "QUAD",
    "hint": "UAD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of juvenile",
    "answer": "JUVEN",
    "hint": "JEN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of theme",
    "answer": "THE",
    "hint": "H",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of alexia",
    "answer": "LEX",
    "hint": "EX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of infrastructure",
    "answer": "INFRA",
    "hint": "RA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of neuralgia",
    "answer": "NEUR",
    "hint": "EU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of binoculars",
    "answer": "BIN",
    "hint": "B",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of quart",
    "answer": "QUART",
    "hint": "UA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of durable",
    "answer": "DUR",
    "hint": "U",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of maniac",
    "answer": "MANIA",
    "hint": "MAN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of theology",
    "answer": "THEO",
    "hint": "EO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of blastula",
    "answer": "BLAST",
    "hint": "BST",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of international",
    "answer": "INTER",
    "hint": "NTE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of misnomer",
    "answer": "NOM",
    "hint": "NM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bursar",
    "answer": "BURS",
    "hint": "BRS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of quintuple",
    "answer": "QUINT",
    "hint": "QIN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of maximize",
    "answer": "MAX",
    "hint": "MX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of calcite",
    "answer": "CALC",
    "hint": "CA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of nonsense",
    "answer": "NON",
    "hint": "N",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of isometric",
    "answer": "ISO",
    "hint": "IS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dynamo",
    "answer": "DYN",
    "hint": "YN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of empathy",
    "answer": "EM",
    "hint": "M",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of candle",
    "answer": "CAND",
    "hint": "AN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of eradicate",
    "answer": "RADIC",
    "hint": "ADI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of thermal",
    "answer": "THERM",
    "hint": "ERM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of retort",
    "answer": "TORT",
    "hint": "OR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of intercept",
    "answer": "INTER",
    "hint": "ER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of xenophobic",
    "answer": "XEN",
    "hint": "X",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of heliograph",
    "answer": "HELI",
    "hint": "HE",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage13 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of radioactive",
    "answer": "RADIO",
    "hint": "AD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of judgment",
    "answer": "JUD",
    "hint": "J",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of annotate",
    "answer": "NOT",
    "hint": "NT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cardiac",
    "answer": "CARDI",
    "hint": "CAD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of engorge",
    "answer": "EN",
    "hint": "E",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of meson",
    "answer": "MESO",
    "hint": "ME",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of attract",
    "answer": "TRACT",
    "hint": "TRC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ramify",
    "answer": "RAM",
    "hint": "RM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of conjunction",
    "answer": "JUNCT",
    "hint": "JCT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of incarnate",
    "answer": "CARN",
    "hint": "CRN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of endogamy",
    "answer": "ENDO",
    "hint": "EO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of intravenous",
    "answer": "INTRA",
    "hint": "IRA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cataclysm",
    "answer": "CATA",
    "hint": "CA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of nominal",
    "answer": "NOMIN",
    "hint": "NOM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of reaction",
    "answer": "RE",
    "hint": "R",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of collaborate",
    "answer": "LAB",
    "hint": "LB",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of perennial",
    "answer": "ENNI",
    "hint": "EI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of kilometer",
    "answer": "KILO",
    "hint": "KO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cauterize",
    "answer": "CAUT",
    "hint": "CA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of rejuvenate",
    "answer": "JUVEN",
    "hint": "JVN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of announce",
    "answer": "NOUN",
    "hint": "NU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cinematography",
    "answer": "MAT",
    "hint": "MT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of lactate",
    "answer": "LACT",
    "hint": "LCT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of regent",
    "answer": "REG",
    "hint": "EG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of telekinesis",
    "answer": "KINE",
    "hint": "NE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of exceed",
    "answer": "CEED",
    "hint": "CE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of inside",
    "answer": "IN",
    "hint": "I",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of innovate",
    "answer": "NOV",
    "hint": "N",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of epilogue",
    "answer": "EPI",
    "hint": "EP",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of transfer",
    "answer": "TRANS",
    "hint": "RNS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of octagon",
    "answer": "OCTA",
    "hint": "OTA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of explosion",
    "answer": "PLOS",
    "hint": "PS",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage14 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of triangle",
    "answer": "TRI",
    "hint": "TR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of enumerate",
    "answer": "NUMER",
    "hint": "NUM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of retrogress",
    "answer": "RETRO",
    "hint": "RTO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of equidistant",
    "answer": "EQUI",
    "hint": "EQ",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of caustic",
    "answer": "CAUST",
    "hint": "CST",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of lactose",
    "answer": "LACTO",
    "hint": "LTO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of object",
    "answer": "OB",
    "hint": "B",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of metaphysics",
    "answer": "META",
    "hint": "TA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ultrahigh",
    "answer": "ULTRA",
    "hint": "ULA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of detoxification",
    "answer": "TOX",
    "hint": "TX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ergonomics",
    "answer": "ERGO",
    "hint": "ERG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bilateral",
    "answer": "LATER",
    "hint": "LTR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of accessible",
    "answer": "CESS",
    "hint": "CS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of enunciate",
    "answer": "NUN",
    "hint": "N",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of rhinoceros",
    "answer": "RHIN",
    "hint": "RN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of opposition",
    "answer": "OP",
    "hint": "P",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of unfair",
    "answer": "UN",
    "hint": "U",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of midway",
    "answer": "MID",
    "hint": "MD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of kinesthesia",
    "answer": "ESTH",
    "hint": "ST",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of mobile",
    "answer": "MOB",
    "hint": "B",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of octopus",
    "answer": "OCTO",
    "hint": "TO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of centennial",
    "answer": "CENT",
    "hint": "CE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of leukemina",
    "answer": "LEUK",
    "hint": "LK",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of rhodopsin",
    "answer": "RHOD",
    "hint": "RD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of alexia",
    "answer": "LEX",
    "hint": "LX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ethnic",
    "answer": "ETHNO",
    "hint": "EHN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of unique",
    "answer": "UNI",
    "hint": "UI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of binoculars",
    "answer": "OCU",
    "hint": "OC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of accelerate",
    "answer": "CELER",
    "hint": "ELE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ridicule",
    "answer": "RID",
    "hint": "R",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of xeric",
    "answer": "XER",
    "hint": "XE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cursive",
    "answer": "CURS",
    "hint": "RS",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage15 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of mortician",
    "answer": "MORT",
    "hint": "MT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of equation",
    "answer": "EQU",
    "hint": "EU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of multimedia",
    "answer": "MULTI",
    "hint": "UTI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of suburb",
    "answer": "URB",
    "hint": "U",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of catarrh",
    "answer": "RRH",
    "hint": "RH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of egocentric",
    "answer": "CENTR",
    "hint": "NTR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of mutant",
    "answer": "MUT",
    "hint": "T",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of liberate",
    "answer": "LIBER",
    "hint": "LBR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of excavate",
    "answer": "EX",
    "hint": "X",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of diode",
    "answer": "OD",
    "hint": "D",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of deodorant",
    "answer": "ODOR",
    "hint": "DO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of linguist",
    "answer": "LINGU",
    "hint": "LGU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of duo",
    "answer": "DUO",
    "hint": "D",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of euphemism",
    "answer": "EU",
    "hint": "E",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of encephalitis",
    "answer": "CEPHO",
    "hint": "EPH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of aesthetic",
    "answer": "AESTH",
    "hint": "STH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of leucine",
    "answer": "LEUC",
    "hint": "EU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cerebral",
    "answer": "CEREB",
    "hint": "ERB",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ascertain",
    "answer": "CERT",
    "hint": "CR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of liposuction",
    "answer": "LIP",
    "hint": "LP",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of extrovert",
    "answer": "EXTRO",
    "hint": "XRO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ruby",
    "answer": "RUB",
    "hint": "RB",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of chromatics",
    "answer": "CHROMAT",
    "hint": "HMA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of optic",
    "answer": "OPT",
    "hint": "P",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of evacuate",
    "answer": "VAC",
    "hint": "AC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of natal",
    "answer": "NAT",
    "hint": "NA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of artifact",
    "answer": "FACT",
    "hint": "FT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of granite",
    "answer": "LITE",
    "hint": "LE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of convention",
    "answer": "VEN",
    "hint": "EN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of homicide",
    "answer": "CIDE",
    "hint": "ID",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of gradual",
    "answer": "GRAD",
    "hint": "RA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of applaud",
    "answer": "PLAUD",
    "hint": "LAU",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage16 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of orthodontist",
    "answer": "ORTHO",
    "hint": "RO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sane",
    "answer": "SAN",
    "hint": "S",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of energy",
    "answer": "ERG",
    "hint": "RG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of naval",
    "answer": "NAV",
    "hint": "N",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cyclone",
    "answer": "CYCL",
    "hint": "YCL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of ascend",
    "answer": "SCEND",
    "hint": "SND",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of extraordinary",
    "answer": "EXTRA",
    "hint": "XTR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dislocate",
    "answer": "LOC",
    "hint": "O",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of confer",
    "answer": "FER",
    "hint": "FR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of outgoing",
    "answer": "OUT",
    "hint": "U",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of clamor",
    "answer": "CLAM",
    "hint": "LAM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of radish",
    "answer": "RADIX",
    "hint": "ADX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of veracity",
    "answer": "VER",
    "hint": "V",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of conscience",
    "answer": "SCI",
    "hint": "SC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of renege",
    "answer": "NEG",
    "hint": "NG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of achromatic",
    "answer": "CHROM",
    "hint": "HRM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of monologue",
    "answer": "LOG",
    "hint": "LG",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of osteopathy",
    "answer": "OSTEO",
    "hint": "OE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of fidelity",
    "answer": "FID",
    "hint": "I",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of neonatal",
    "answer": "NEO",
    "hint": "EO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of verbalize",
    "answer": "VERB",
    "hint": "ER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of flexible",
    "answer": "FLECT",
    "hint": "FLE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sclerometer",
    "answer": "SCLER",
    "hint": "LE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of clarification",
    "answer": "CLAR",
    "hint": "AR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of eloquent",
    "answer": "LOQU",
    "hint": "OQ",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of octagon",
    "answer": "OCTA",
    "hint": "OCT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of nondescript",
    "answer": "NON",
    "hint": "NO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of orthography",
    "answer": "ORTHO",
    "hint": "OTH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of enumerate",
    "answer": "NUMER",
    "hint": "NUM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of florist",
    "answer": "FLEUR",
    "hint": "FEU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of concurrent",
    "answer": "CURR",
    "hint": "CU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of immerge",
    "answer": "MERGE",
    "hint": "ERG",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage17 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of inscribe",
    "answer": "SCRIBE",
    "hint": "SRI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of overstock",
    "answer": "OVER",
    "hint": "OV",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of chrysanthemum",
    "answer": "CHRYS",
    "hint": "CRY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of monolith",
    "answer": "LITH",
    "hint": "LH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of introvert",
    "answer": "VERT",
    "hint": "ER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of notarize",
    "answer": "NOT",
    "hint": "NT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of osteology",
    "answer": "OSTEO",
    "hint": "OTE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of forfeited",
    "answer": "FOR",
    "hint": "OR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of secede",
    "answer": "SE",
    "hint": "S",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of conclusion",
    "answer": "CLUS",
    "hint": "CS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of paleontology",
    "answer": "PALE",
    "hint": "AL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of reverse",
    "answer": "VERS",
    "hint": "ER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of oxidize",
    "answer": "OXI",
    "hint": "X",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of elocution",
    "answer": "LOCU",
    "hint": "OC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of vice",
    "answer": "VICE",
    "hint": "IC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of prelude",
    "answer": "LUD",
    "hint": "LU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of fracture",
    "answer": "FRACT",
    "hint": "RAC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of parasite",
    "answer": "PARA",
    "hint": "AR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of exclaim",
    "answer": "CLAIM",
    "hint": "AI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of autopsy",
    "answer": "OPS",
    "hint": "OS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of reside",
    "answer": "SID",
    "hint": "SD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of oxidize",
    "answer": "OXY",
    "hint": "OY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of tractor",
    "answer": "TRACT",
    "hint": "RAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of refuge",
    "answer": "FUG",
    "hint": "FU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of selfish",
    "answer": "SELF",
    "hint": "SF",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of illusion",
    "answer": "LUS",
    "hint": "LU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pedal",
    "answer": "PED",
    "hint": "PD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of chronic",
    "answer": "CHRON",
    "hint": "HRO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of forebode",
    "answer": "FORE",
    "hint": "OR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of evident",
    "answer": "VID",
    "hint": "V",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of structure",
    "answer": "STRUCT",
    "hint": "TUC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hectoliter",
    "answer": "HECT",
    "hint": "EC",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage18 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of convince",
    "answer": "VINCE",
    "hint": "VIC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pedestrian",
    "answer": "PEDE",
    "hint": "ED",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of lumen",
    "answer": "LUMIN",
    "hint": "LIN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of oxymoron",
    "answer": "OXY",
    "hint": "OY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of fragment",
    "answer": "FRAG",
    "hint": "RA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of chrysolite",
    "answer": "CHRYSO",
    "hint": "HRY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of semicircle",
    "answer": "SEMI",
    "hint": "EM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of retort",
    "answer": "TORT",
    "hint": "ORT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of compel",
    "answer": "PEL",
    "hint": "PL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of incisor",
    "answer": "CISE",
    "hint": "IS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of victory",
    "answer": "VIC",
    "hint": "VC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of malfunction",
    "answer": "FUNCT",
    "hint": "UNC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of september",
    "answer": "SEPT",
    "hint": "SE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of lunatic",
    "answer": "LUNA",
    "hint": "UN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of seclude",
    "answer": "CLUD",
    "hint": "LU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of tetrose",
    "answer": "TETRA",
    "hint": "ETR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of technocracy",
    "answer": "TECHNO",
    "hint": "THN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of vision",
    "answer": "VIS",
    "hint": "VI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of macroevolution",
    "answer": "MACRO",
    "hint": "ACR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of conserve",
    "answer": "SERV",
    "hint": "SR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of inclination",
    "answer": "CLINE",
    "hint": "CLI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pedicure",
    "answer": "PEDI",
    "hint": "PED",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of confusion",
    "answer": "FUS",
    "hint": "FS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of toxicology",
    "answer": "FOX",
    "hint": "FX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of gastric",
    "answer": "GASTR",
    "hint": "GST",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sextet",
    "answer": "SEX",
    "hint": "SX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of magnify",
    "answer": "MAGNI",
    "hint": "MNI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of coauthor",
    "answer": "CO",
    "hint": "C",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pentathlon",
    "answer": "PENT",
    "hint": "PNT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of evident",
    "answer": "VID",
    "hint": "V",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of commemorate",
    "answer": "MEMOR",
    "hint": "MER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of xanthium",
    "answer": "XANTH",
    "hint": "XTH",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage19 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of supersonic",
    "answer": "SUPER",
    "hint": "SER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of bankrupt",
    "answer": "RUPT",
    "hint": "RPT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of stellar",
    "answer": "STELL",
    "hint": "SL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of desolate",
    "answer": "SOL",
    "hint": "SL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of maneuver",
    "answer": "MANI",
    "hint": "MAN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of gerontocracy",
    "answer": "GER",
    "hint": "GR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of gerontocracy",
    "answer": "COM",
    "hint": "CM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of summit",
    "answer": "SUM",
    "hint": "SM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of revival",
    "answer": "VIV",
    "hint": "VI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of dyspepsia",
    "answer": "PEPS",
    "hint": "PS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of command",
    "answer": "MAND",
    "hint": "MD",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of insomnia",
    "answer": "SOMN",
    "hint": "SM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of egomania",
    "answer": "MANIA",
    "hint": "MAN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of vital",
    "answer": "VIT",
    "hint": "IT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of collision",
    "answer": "COL",
    "hint": "C",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of perennial",
    "answer": "PER",
    "hint": "PR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of retrogress",
    "answer": "RETRO",
    "hint": "RET",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of quarter",
    "answer": "QUART",
    "hint": "QRT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of advocate",
    "answer": "VOC",
    "hint": "VC",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of stationery",
    "answer": "STA",
    "hint": "S",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of esophagus",
    "answer": "PHAG",
    "hint": "PA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of consonant",
    "answer": "SON",
    "hint": "SN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of cosmonaut",
    "answer": "COSMO",
    "hint": "COM",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of magnate",
    "answer": "MAGNA",
    "hint": "AGNA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of gastronomy",
    "answer": "GASTRO",
    "hint": "AO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of agronomy",
    "answer": "AGRI",
    "hint": "AI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of granary",
    "answer": "GRAN",
    "hint": "GR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of sophism",
    "answer": "SOPH",
    "hint": "SPH",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of egomania",
    "answer": "MANIA",
    "hint": "MNI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of craniology",
    "answer": "LOGY",
    "hint": "LY",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of melanoma",
    "answer": "MELAN",
    "hint": "MLN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of helicopter",
    "answer": "HELIC",
    "hint": "HLI",
    "solved": 1
  },
];

var stage20 = [
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "What city is the capital of decagon",
    "answer": "GON",
    "hint": "GN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What city is the capital of session",
    "answer": "SESS",
    "hint": "SE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What city is the capital of peptic",
    "answer": "PEPT",
    "hint": "PET",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What city is the capital of benevolent",
    "answer": "VOL",
    "hint": "VO",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What city is the capital of carnivorous",
    "answer": "VOR",
    "hint": "V",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What city is the capital of chlorophyll",
    "answer": "PHYLL",
    "hint": "PYL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What city is the capital of gratify",
    "answer": "GRAT",
    "hint": "RA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What city is the capital of circumspect",
    "answer": "SPEC",
    "hint": "SPE",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What city is the capital of microcosm",
    "answer": "COSM",
    "hint": "CS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What city is the capital of podiatry",
    "answer": "IATRO",
    "hint": "IAT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What city is the capital of inspire",
    "answer": "SPIR",
    "hint": "SPR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What city is the capital of maximal",
    "answer": "MAX",
    "hint": "MX",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What city is the capital of pseudopod",
    "answer": "POD",
    "hint": "O",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What city is the capital of biosphere",
    "answer": "SPHERE",
    "hint": "PER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What city is the capital of medieval",
    "answer": "MEDI",
    "hint": "ED",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What city is the capital of crucial",
    "answer": "CRUC",
    "hint": "RU",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What city is the capital of peripheral",
    "answer": "PERI",
    "hint": "ER",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What city is the capital of gynephobia",
    "answer": "GYN",
    "hint": "GN",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What city is the capital of devour",
    "answer": "VOUR",
    "hint": "VUR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What city is the capital of astronaut",
    "answer": "ASTRO",
    "hint": "STR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What city is the capital of xyloid",
    "answer": "XYL",
    "hint": "YL",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What city is the capital of heliotrope",
    "answer": "HELIO",
    "hint": "HLI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What city is the capital of inspire",
    "answer": "SPIR",
    "hint": "SR",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What city is the capital of digression",
    "answer": "GRESS",
    "hint": "GRS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What city is the capital of accumulate",
    "answer": "CUMUL",
    "hint": "CML",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What city is the capital of physical",
    "answer": "PHYS",
    "hint": "PHS",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What city is the capital of megalopolis",
    "answer": "MEGA",
    "hint": "MA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What city is the capital of hemispere",
    "answer": "HEMI",
    "hint": "HI",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What city is the capital of stable",
    "answer": "STA",
    "hint": "SA",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What city is the capital of epiphyte",
    "answer": "PHYTO",
    "hint": "PHT",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What city is the capital of icon",
    "answer": "ICON",
    "hint": "ION",
    "solved": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What city is the capital of controversy",
    "answer": "CONTRO",
    "hint": "CTR",
    "solved": 1
  },
];
